

## **KONTAKTUPPGIFTER**

Vikingavägen 11B, Lund

+46763222767

shariati.sam@gmail.com

https://samshariati.github.io/

# **SKILLS**

- Computer proficiency
- Game design
- C#
- C++
- Unity
- Maya
- Visual Studio
- HTML
- CSS
- Game developer
- Board game developer

LANGUAG	ES		
Svenska:			C2
Flytande nivå			
Engelska:			C2
Flytande nivå			
Persiska:			C2
Flytande nivå			

# Sam Shariati

#### **SUMMARY**

Recently graduated in Computer Science with a focus on game development at Malmö University, and have a strong interest in entering the job market to apply my knowledge in practice. I am a hard-working, communicative and engaged person. I look forward to an opportunity to gain more work experience.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Full-time Employment** 03/2020 - pågående **Coop Annehem -** Lund

Shop assistant

**Hourly Employment** 07/2018 - 12/2019 **Palm&Partners -** Malmö

• Production work

• Warehouse work

· Forklift operator

**Hourly Employment** 12/2017 - 01/2018

StudentConsulting - Malmö

• Warehouse work at Postnord terminal

**Part-time Employment** 06/2017 - 07/2017

Netto livsmedelsbutik - Halmstad

**Temporary Employment** 04/2016 - 05/2016

Ergohuset - Malmö

**Part-time Employment** 11/2015 - 04/2016

Kronans apotek - Lund

**Full-time Employment** 08/2015 - 10/2015

Shell - Vadsö, Norge

• Gas station

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor's Degree:** Computer Science in Game Development **Malmö University** - Malmö

High School Education: Natural Science programme

Polhemskolan - Lund

# **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

I am a game developer in my spare time, where I create both board and digital games.